It is a period of civil war. Rebel spaceships, striking from a hidden base, have won 
their first victory against the evil Galactic Empire.
During the battle, rebel spies managed to steal secret plans to the Empire's ultimate 
weapon, the DEATH STAR, an armored space station with enough power to destroy an entire 
planet.
Pursued by the Empire's sinister agents, Princess Leia races home aboard her starship, 
custodian of the stolen plans that can save her people and restore freedom to the galaxy.

It is a dark time for the Rebellion. Although the Death Star has been destroyed, Imperial 
troops have driven the Rebel forces from their hidden base and pursued them across the 
galaxy.
Evading the dreaded Imperial Starfleet, a group of freedom fighters led by Luke Skywalker 
has established a new secret base on the remote ice world of Hoth.
The evil lord Darth Vader, obsessed with finding young Skywalker, has dispatched thousands 
of remote probes into the far reaches of space.

Luke Skywalker has returned to his home planet of Tatooine in an attempt to rescue his 
friend Han Solo from the clutches of the vile gangster Jabba the Hutt.
Little does Luke know that the GALACTIC EMPIRE has secretly begun construction on a new 
armored space station even more powerful than the first dreaded Death Star.
When completed, this ultimate weapon will spell certain doom for the small band of rebels 
struggling to restore freedom to the galaxy.
